(massage) ayo don't talk shit bout me twin, all these bitches talking shit bout me. but fuck em...im not give a shit. im build diffrent u'know what im saying. i keep that grind up and make sum honey buns twin, they aint no me
Riding trought night don't, don't need fake shit
been geeked up, yeah no stress
diamonds on my neck yeah..were full icing (ICE)
gang pulled up yeah, were flying
geeked were geeked up for life he (its lit)
diamonds on my cruise yeah
diamonds at the both yeah, we on X like we on cush ye (ya ya)
ain't no talking to me if you lying
yeah shawty we're flying
Riding trought night don't, need fake shit
ain't no talking to me if you lying
shawtys all over me they're crying...over me, i don't play some games
if you say we got beef i shoot u in you crip
diamonds shine wide, feeling wildly
no stress on me keep grinding
she's funky bout me i keep it funking
still grinding in tha game
i aint got cheap cologne
bullet flying i kept reload (reload)
still grinding on tha trance, i feel blessed
on a trance, on a trance
we're in tha game
whole team loud we partying loud
still grinding on tha trance, i feel blessed
on a trance, on a trance
its all i know
Riding trought night don't, don't need fake shit
been geeked up, yeah no stress
diamonds on my neck yeah..were full icing (ICE)
everything shine when i step out
Ice in my veins she's full on my arms (yeah yeah)
don't do smoke king or i shoot you out
im shine im flying
on a trance, on a trance
Riding trought night don't, don't need fake shit
been geeked up, yeah no stress
ghost in her face ghost in the past (ya ya)
still grinding in tha game
i aint got cheap cologne
bullet flying i kept reload (reload)
still grinding on tha trance, i feel blessed
on a trance, on a trance
we're in tha game
whole team loud we partying
still grinding on tha trance, i feel blessed
on a trance, on a trance
its all i know
whole team loud
on a trance, on a trance
(yeah yeah yaaaaaaa)
(ya ya)
(yeah yeah yaaaa)